Mr. Lin,
السيد لين،
someone just delivered this to you.
قام أحدهم بتسليم هذا إليك للتو.
Why are you so nervous?
لماذا أنت متوتر للغاية؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
You don't want to admit it?
ألا تريد الاعتراف بذلك؟
Give me some time.
أعطني بعض الوقت.
I'll think about it.
سأفكر في الأمر.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Then you get some rest.
ثم تحصل على قسط من الراحة.
I have something to do.
لديّ شيءٌ عليّ فعله.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Where's Lu Xing?
أين لو شينغ؟
Lu Xing?
لو شينغ؟
Do you know him?
هل تعرفه؟
Cut the crap.
كفى هراءً.
Has he come to you?
هل جاء إليك؟
I thought he was important to you.
كنت أظن أنه كان مهماً بالنسبة لك.
It seems not.
يبدو أن الأمر ليس كذلك.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
What happened to Xing?
ماذا حدث لـ Xing؟
What's your relationship?
ما هي علاقتكما؟
He's been missing for three days.
لقد فُقد منذ ثلاثة أيام.
As for our relationship,
أما بالنسبة لعلاقتنا،
he is just
إنه فقط
he's just a dog I picked up.
إنه مجرد كلب التقطته.
Say something!
قل شيئا!
Are you mute?
هل أنت أبكم؟
Do you know your life is mine?
هل تعلم أن حياتك هي حياتي؟
If you don't tell me the truth,
إذا لم تقل لي الحقيقة،
I'll throw you out right now.
سأطردك الآن.
Stay by my side.
ابقَ بجانبي.
I'm the only one who can help you now.
أنا الشخص الوحيد الذي يستطيع مساعدتك الآن.
[So he sacrificed so much for me,]
[لذا فقد ضحى بالكثير من أجلي]
[and almost died in the hands of Lin Mojiao.]
[وكاد يموت على يد لين موجياو.]
[I didn't contact Lu Xing because I didn't want him to get involved.]
[لم أتصل بلو شينغ لأنني لم أرغب في تورطه.]
[I didn't expect this to happen.]
[لم أتوقع حدوث هذا.]
I only met Lu Xing once in the Hidden Tower.
لم أقابل لو شينغ إلا مرة واحدة في البرج الخفي.
If you know
إذا كنت تعرف
his whereabouts,
مكان وجوده،
please tell me.
أرجوك أخبرني.
I'm worried about him.
أنا قلق عليه.
What?
ماذا؟
You're not satisfied with Lin Moqing,
أنت غير راضٍ عن لين موكينغ،
and you're also interested in Lu Xing?
وهل أنت مهتم أيضاً بلو شينغ؟
You're so annoying.
أنت مزعج للغاية.
But I tell you,
لكنني أقول لكم،
you can't have
لا يمكنك الحصول على
either of them.
أي منهما.
Maybe you should figure out
ربما عليك أن تكتشف
who you really care about.
من تهتم لأمرهم حقاً.
Wenjie,
وينجي،
ask your heart.
اسأل قلبك.
Mind your own business.
اهتم بشؤونك الخاصة.
Look at you, all smiles.
انظر إليك، كل هذه الابتسامات.
Your brother
أخوك
must be furious with you.
لا بد أنني غاضب منك بشدة.
I'm just
أنا فقط
fighting fire with fire.
مكافحة النار بالنار.
What are the conditions?
ما هي الشروط؟
The other party wants
الطرف الآخر يريد
two hundred million.
مئتا مليون.
Two hundred million?
مئتا مليون؟
What a coincidence.
يا لها من مصادفة!
Give him.
أعطه إياه.
Besides these two hundred million,
إلى جانب هذين المئتي مليون،
I'll give you another big gift.
سأقدم لك هدية كبيرة أخرى.
Do you want to have dinner together tonight?
هل ترغب بتناول العشاء معًا الليلة؟
I have a big gift for you.
لدي هدية كبيرة لك.
No. I'm on a diet.
لا، أنا أتبع حمية غذائية.
You're not fat.
أنت لست سميناً.
You should eat more.
يجب أن تأكل أكثر.
Get fat and go back...
اكتسب وزناً زائداً ثم عد أدراجك...
I think
أظن
you and Miss Blue
أنتِ والآنسة بلو
must have something going on.
لا بد أن هناك شيئاً ما يحدث.
What does it have to do with you?
ما علاقة ذلك بك؟
Don't blame me for not warning you.
لا تلومني لعدم تحذيرك.
With the way you are now,
على حالك الآن،
what will happen to your plan later?
ماذا سيحدث لخطتك لاحقاً؟
If she finds out about what you've done...
إذا علمت بما فعلت...
We'll talk about it later.
سنتحدث عن ذلك لاحقاً.
Talk about it later?
هل نتحدث عن ذلك لاحقاً؟
Let's see how you'll explain it.
لنرى كيف ستشرح ذلك.
Don't blame me for not reminding you.
لا تلومني لعدم تذكيرك.
With the way you are now,
على حالك الآن،
what will happen to the plan later?
ماذا سيحدث للخطة لاحقاً؟
If she finds out what you've done...
إذا اكتشفت ما فعلته...
This is for you.
هذا لك.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
It's not me again, is it?
أليس هذا أنا مجدداً؟
You thought the last doll was ugly, right?
لقد ظننت أن الدمية الأخيرة كانت قبيحة، أليس كذلك؟
I made a pretty one for you.
لقد صنعت واحدة جميلة من أجلك.
Is this pretty?
هل هذا جميل؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
As pretty as you.
جميلة مثلك.
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
What's the big gift
ما هي الهدية الكبيرة؟
you mentioned last time?
هل ذكرت ذلك في المرة الماضية؟
Are you
أنت
willing to...
على استعداد لـ...
Is this the big gift?
هل هذه هي الهدية الكبرى؟
Xing.
شينغ.
I'll take you away.
سآخذك بعيداً.
Water.
ماء.
I want water.
أريد ماءً.
Give me water.
أعطني ماءً.
It's all my fault.
كل هذا خطأي.
I shouldn't have trusted Lin Moqing
ما كان ينبغي لي أن أثق في لين موكينغ
and lost you.
وفقدتك.
Vivi, don't worry.
فيفي، لا تقلقي.
I'll find Xu Meng.
سأجد شو مينغ.
If you hadn't taken her away,
لو لم تكن قد أخذتها بعيدًا،
she wouldn't have disappeared.
لم تكن لتختفي.
Trust me,
ثق بي،
I'll find her.
سأجدها.
I trusted you last time
لقد وثقت بك في المرة الماضية
and agreed to work with you.
ووافقت على العمل معك.
What about now?
وماذا عن الآن؟
You want me to believe you again?
هل تريدني أن أصدقك مرة أخرى؟
Vivi.
أنت حي.
I'm warning you.
أنا أحذرك.
If anything happens to her,
إذا حدث لها أي مكروه،
our cooperation will end here.
سينتهي تعاوننا هنا.
I will also take back the authorization
سأسحب أيضاً التفويض
of the resort.
المنتجع.
Find Xu Meng
ابحث عن شو مينغ
at all costs.
بأي ثمن.
Xing.
شينغ.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I know where she is.
أعرف مكانها.
She must have been here.
لا بد أنها كانت هنا.
She must have been moved by Lin Mojiao.
لا بد أنها تأثرت بلين موجياو.